They say I'm a charmer.
I charm my hustles.
Well, that comes after
dealing with women, you know.
After hairdressing.
I love to dress hair.
I kind of think of myself as an artist.
I treat people the way
most people don't treat 'em
and they give me a lot of respect.
No matter if I have my hand
in their pocket, you know.
But being I know what to do, you know,
being hip enough to know, I do it.
It's love and peace.
Love and peace.
You just gotta keep sending
it out, love and peace.
Love that love and peace.
I'm not J for nothing, you know.
Excuse me, ma'am?
Where's the safe?
What?
We're here for the safe.
Does Harry know about this?
Yeah, Harry phoned us this morning
and said we pick up the safe.
Says it's behind the cash register.
I don't know anything
about picking up a safe.
Look, I made a special trip
up here with the schvartze.
Harry didn't tell me anything about it.
Harry didn't tell you anything about it?
No.
Okay, come on.
Harry didn't tell her anything about it.
Well, if Harry didn't tell
you anything about it,
then you explain it to Harry, okay?
Hey, wait a minute, mister.
Wait, wait, wait, come back.
Harry doesn't always tell me everything.
I only work here part-time,
a couple of nights a week
because my husband just had an operation.
I'm sorry to hear that.
It was terrible, he had
a growth in his rear end.
Oh, that can be very painful.
You're telling me,
lays around the house
all day long complaining.
Get me this, get me that.
Have you tried an enema?
Mister, the last thing in the world
that my husband needs
right now is an enema.
I didn't meant your husband,
have you tried an enema?
Me?
- Have I tried an enema?
- Yeah.
Are you kidding?
Have I tried an enema?
You gotta be crazy, have I tried an enema?
Goodbye, darling.
Goodbye, sweetheart.
- Hey, but what about Harry?
- Yeah.
What about Harry?
What shall I tell him?
Tell him to take an enema.
Hey, Harry.
What is it?
Harry, the guys were just here
and they picked up the safe.
What?
Stop that man, help!
Stop that man, police!
Police!
J!
Hi.
Can I have a lift?
Where are you going?
Home.
Where's home?
It's not very far.
Get in.
You really have a lot of keys.
My goodness, this your car?
Yeah.
A lot of plastic.
I asked for leather all over
here and they gave me vinyl.
Right.
But it's better to have a
car than not to have a car.
That's true.
Would you?
Would you like a key?
I'll bet this is your car.
- Right.
Do you want the key that
starts the car or do you
- prefer the challenge.
- No, I prefer the challenge.
I prefer the challenge
of trying to find the keys out of this.
Can I try it?
Did you try this one yet?
Yes, that's the first one I tried.
Actually, that's the key
to my locker at the gym.
- This key here.
- Your locker at the gym?
Yes, I bet you don't
know what this key is.
That's Frank's locker at the gym.
No, no, actually, it's Bruce's locker.
This is Frank's.
Where we sure are hitting it off.
Nervous?
Me, nervous?
Are you nervous?
I am.
You rich?
Why?
Does it matter?
All right, this is a stick-up.
No, no, no.
I want your diamonds and your minks
and your credit cards and your whatnot.
Take everything.
Everything?
Come here, Kitty.
Come here, kitty, kitty, kitty, Kitty,
Kitty, Kitty, Kitty, kitty.
This is my cat, Nathan.
How are you, Nathan?
He doesn't like you.
He's very talkative.
That's okay, I like you.
- Do you?
- Mm-hmm.
What has four legs and chases cats?
I don't know.
Mrs. Katz and her lawyer.
Oh, that's very sad.
You're a married man.
What?
No, not really.
Not really, no.
Why?
What happened?
She was sneak cheating.
I came home one day, there
was this guy in the closet
on his knees with a cigar in his mouth.
He said, "This ain't what you think."
I said, "I don't care what it is, pal,
just don't do nothing
in front of the kids."
You have kids.
Oh, yeah.
How many?
Oh, nine, 10.
10 or 11.
About two.
Where are they now?
I don't know.
You're a loner?
Oh, no.
I got a lot of friends.
I really like you.
What?
I said, I really like you.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm a charmer.
I think you're nifty.
Nifty?
I mean, nice,
I can tell you're nice.
I'm a natural.
That's cute.
Thank you.
You look like Little Miss Muffet.
Why?
My breasts are too small?
Too small for what?
What are you doing?
I really don't know.
You're wearing your socks to bed.
Yeah.
That's a very bad sign.
It means you're going to leave quick.
Oh, yeah.
You always wear your sweater to bed?
Yeah, well, I think my
breasts are too small.
What?
Kiss it.
Kiss it?
I love to have my arms kissed.
What's so great about that?
"Born to win."
Are you born to win?
You better believe it.
What's that?
That's where I get my vitamin shots.
Vitamin, vitamin B52.
It's good for my memory.
You got a nice body on you.
You don't think
my breasts are too small?
Yeah.
They're bigger than mine.
Parm.
Geek, my man.
The name is Vivian, dope fiend.
How're ya doing, JJ?
You know, I'd like to take care of you.
A friend of mine should be coming by.
I have a job for you.
No, man, I can't.
This is easy.
All you have to do is take a package
from person A to person B.
What do you want from me?
Want?
You're the one who wants.
Man, you got everything.
You got your chicks,
you got your limousine.
Give me a few bags on credit.
Oh, JJ.
Man, you've got my
wife hustling for you.
You want her with some spade?
You know there's nothing
lower than a junkie chick, JJ.
Come on.
Come on, now.
She'll be very happy to see you.
We'll do some work and
then I'll fix you up.
- Hi, JJ, how are you?
- Hi, Marlene.
- How are you?
Good.
What can I do?
I got something for Stanley.
Ooh, un petit moment, mon cheri.
You're looking good.
Thank you, you too.
Stanley, it's JJ.
Hi, JJ.
How are you, Stanley?
I got something for you.
You got something for me?
A little taste?
You'll get yours from the Geek.
You know, the Geek, Stanley.
Hey, listen.
About Marlene's hair.
I was looking at it.
She's got kind of a,
well, she's got kind of a
Bronx look, you know, Stanley.
I was thinking I could give her a more
of a Manhattan look, you know.
Like a cap cut, you know.
What?
A cap cut, you know,
like Sassoon.
Vidal Sassoon.
It's very in, Stanley.
Bye, JJ, see you around.
Geek?
Geek, buddy.
Geek.
Geek?
Don't forget me.
My geek.
- Geek, we had a deal.
- Oh, J.
- You promised.
- Where have you been?
You know where I've been.
Was it difficult?
No, kick cold turkey,
lay around in jail 18 months, nothing.
I'm sorry.
How are the kids?
They're with my mother in California.
Geek, you got something for me?
Vivian's the name, JJ.
Right.
Then let's hear it.
Vivian.
You haven't been
around for a while, J.
I took a bust.
Yeah, I heard about that.
Some junkie chick ratted on you.
Yeah.
Well, it's them junkie chicks, J.
What can I say?
Okay.
Why did you let me catch that fall?
You were supposed to watch over me.
I dream about you
almost every night.
Even in jail.
Can I come back to you?
No, J.
Why did you mess me up like this?
Why?
Geek.
You owe me some money.
You got yours in dope.
Four lousy bags.
I never thought you'd turn on a friend.
Who's a friend?
I'm an acquaintance.
Geek.
You're messing with
some bad people, man.
All right, so there's a fortune
in dope up there, you know,
but to deliver the dope one day
and take the cat off the next,
man, you gotta be insane.
Billy, I've gotta hit big and clear out.
That guy Stanley, what's his thing, man?
What is he into?
Businessman, regardless.
He's strictly a profiteer.
He don't even use.
Are you sure the dude's out?
Qui est lá?
Mr. Charm.
JJ.
You guessed it.
- Hiya.
- Hi.
- Stanley isn't home.
- I know.
You wanna come in?
It's up to you.
Okay, come in.
This is my friend.
He's black, you don't
mind black folks, do you?
No.
Does he have a name?
Do you have a name?
Just call me the bogeyman.
Just sit over there.
Sit, sit, sit.
So, Stanley's out on the island?
- Mm-hm, business.
- Business.
He's all business, that Stanley.
I wanna pick up that package
that I dropped off yesterday.
You what?
The package.
I want it back.
You got your money, JJ.
Somebody else got the
money, I got kadoches.
Yeah, well, that's your business.
I have nothing to do with that.
Marlene, this is a take-off.
You gotta be kidding.
No, I'm not kidding.
This is a take-off.
Come on, Marlene, give
me the goodies, come on.
Oh, listen,
- I don't know where the.
- Now, look, lady,
if you don't own up to that package,
I'm gonna take all your furs and jewels
and shove 'em down your throat.
That's about the size of it, Marlene.
Hey, listen, you're not
gonna hurt me, are you?
No, no, I'm not a violent person.
I'm all peace and love.
Oh, JJ, Stanley's gonna kill me.
Stanley always had a lousy attitude.
Come on.
Would you give me a taste?
I didn't know you indulged.
Stanley doesn't even know.
No, man.
I think some other
time is better, Marlene.
Boy...
C'est la vie, Marlene.
- Let's go, JJ!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Cops.
All right, freeze!
Police.
Oh, look, baby.
We got guns, baby.
Split up!
Get him!
Hold it!
Did you get your rocks off?
Not yet.
I'm gonna get 'em off now.
Eddie?
I'm in here, Danny, I got one.
I lost the other one,
but I got the package here.
Come on, spread 'em.
I got a freako with an attitude.
I know him, it's JJ.
- How ya doin', J?
- Move it.
Come on.
Not too good, man.
I got him up on a stick-up, what was it?
'67, '68.
I had him cold.
He talked and he walked, didn't you, babe?
That's the name of the game.
Talk and walk.
Yeah, you should have
done five years minimum
at least on that, J.
I had nothing to do with that.
These guys came up from Florida.
I told you, I introduced them to a party
and this party beats "em.
So in retaliation they made up this story
that J and a friend of
his got these ice picks,
and stuck 'em up and took
$800 outta their backpack,
which is ridiculous.
Anyway, there's some smack here.
Hi, lady.
Well, lady, we're making an arrest.
You might stepping outside if you want.
I don't care what you're doing,
the things people are doing in this house,
you wouldn't believe.
You guys are embarrassing me.
All right, I've had
enough of your lip, J.
We'll I take a little walk in the hallway.
Where are we going?
Hey, lady!
Lady, it's police brutality, lady!
- Come on.
- They're gonna beat me up!
We're gonna put you on
ice for a long time, J.
Danny?
Give me a break, will ya?
I'm trying to wipe jones
completely out of me.
Come on, come on, get up.
I'm slipping up in my jail time.
Three months here and five months there.
I just pulled a year and
a half up at Danbury.
I'm only out three months, Danny.
God, I'm tired, man.
I'm just physically tired.
Don't chain me up.
Please, don't chain me up, Danny.
Hey, look.
Hey, J, look.
J, look, you're gonna have
to take a big fall, baby, you know.
You wanna play, you gotta
pay, baby, you know that.
When you pitch, J, you gotta catch.
- Please, please.
- Now, come on.
Cool, nice and cool, that's it.
How about the Geek?
Come on, J, you know
the Geek, don't you?
Yeah, I know him.
But where does he hang out?
Open End, 77th and 1st.
We're gonna get the Geek, J,
and you're gonna get him for us.
Do you understand?
All right.
From now on, you're gonna keep
on walking and talking, baby.
Hi, sweetheart.
What kind of freak idea was that?
Taking poor Stanley off.
I never did that.
You're really, really
in trouble with him, JJ.
Oh, what did he say?
Well, he wants to pass you a hot shot.
Strychnine, battery acid.
Take your choice.
What can I say?
Stanley wants to ice you.
Screw him where he breeds.
So I've been racking my brain.
What can I do for JJ?
Give him a nice score, 500, 1,000.
You'd do that for me?
But first you have to
do a little job for me.
Geek, if I could break
out of this town, man,
I'd kiss your feet.
Not here, J.
Just do the job.
Right, right.
Drive out to Kennedy
Airport tomorrow morning.
9AM, flight from Paris.
Wear a red tie.
What's it worth?
20 years.
I know that, man.
I mean my price.
800.
And a few bags.
I'm not addicted, I'm habituated.
You know?
Tomorrow, when I get
the money from the guy,
we're gonna get out of here.
We're gonna take a trip
and I'm gonna get clean.
Like that.
"Cause, you know,
it's the environment that Kills you.
You know, it's these greasy junkies
that I gotta hang out
with, you know and whatnot.
You can't trust any of them.
I trust you.
You could ask me anything.
How many men you gone to bed with?
60?
Who's that?
Me over there?
Who's the little guy on the end?
I didn't see you for two days.
Did you like him?
I loved him.
Oh, J!
I was just kidding about all those men, J!
Don't you know that's you?
Just a natural born freak
collector, aren't you?
You're tiptoeing around junk now
because you think it's so hip.
Now, pretty soon, you'll
wanna be dipping and dabbing,
and then you'll end up with a habit,
and take your tail out in the street
and you'll be selling it for junk.
J, don't want all
those things to happen.
I want us to be like regular people.
I'm sorry.
I'm a little moochy.
Do you have to do this?
Sometimes I feel
I just wanna turn my
head around, you know.
You know, I'm a very boring
guy when I'm straight.
Kitty.
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Where are you going?
Wait for me.
I have to take care
of that job, I told you.
- I'm coming.
- No, you can't come.
- Oh, yes, I can.
- No, you can't.
Listen.
I'm only gonna be gone a couple of hours.
I'll be back with a lot of money
and then we can do anything we want.
I don't believe you.
Don't you trust me?
No, let's go.
Wait a second.
If they catch you, it's gonna be 20 years.
You're gonna be in jail for 20 years.
If you don't let me go with you,
I'm gonna scream all over the city.
No, you're not.
He's completely dead, that guy.
Listen, you know that for $342,
we can get a round-trip ticket to Bermuda?
For two?
Yup, we can go right away.
Look, I gotta deliver the package,
pick up my pay and then we're off.
Okay.
I'm looking for Ray.
Third floor, number 47.
Spooky.
What is that, Mafia?
No Mafia.
Business people.
Square, respectable
business people, let's go.
God, they're cutting us off.
Move it!
Baby, get outta here!
Where's my goods?
I don't.
I'll tell ya.
A friend of mine's got 'em.
Where is he?
He's around town, upside down.
I need a phone.
Take me to a phone.
Tell him you've
got a buyer, we'll pick him up.
Okay.
Is Billy Dynamite there?
He's not there.
That's the best I could do.
Take your clothes off.
What?
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
When I get my package,
maybe you get your clothes.
Everything.
Put him in the room in back.
Hey, listen.
You know, he's a junkie.
He may not be back for days.
Well, I guess you got
a streak of bad luck, J.
Hello.
And look at this.
Yes!
Is that your mother?
Oh, yes!
Yes, call the police, yes!
Come in, Stanley.
You got a light?
Get off the bed.
What's he doing in there?
Open up, police, police.
Police?
I'm getting the hell outta here!
Come on, let's go!
Can I help you, sir?
Yeah, I'd like to
see some of your jackets.
What did you have in mind?
Maybe some new double length.
Right over this way, sir.
Excuse me for a moment.
What exactly did you have in mind?
Hey, buddy, what do you get for this?
I'm sorry.
It's just that I was so scared.
I thought they'd killed you.
I was set up.
The Geek set me up.
I don't understand it.
I keep getting beat.
I keep getting beat, I'm sick of it!
I'm sick of it.
We can go away somewhere.
We can get in the car and go anywhere.
Right away.
I was so scared.
- Are you happy?
- Yes.
- Is it gonna be okay?
And we're gonna have a good time?
Yes.
- For a long time?
- Yes.
- For all the time?
- Even maybe all the time.
- Yes.
- And you like my neck?
- I love your neck.
And you really wanna kiss my neck.
Yeah, yeah.
- You're gonna kiss my neck.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're filthy.
When she got there, her cupboard was bare,
so her poor dog had none.
Have you notice, nursery
rhymes don't rhyme.
To get her poor dog a bone,
when she got there, the cupboard was bare,
so she had known.
It really was wonderful.
It was wonderful.
- It was nothing.
- And it's not.
It was nothing, you weren't me.
If you'd been where I was,
it'd have been wonderful.
I'll tell you another nursery rhyme
if you wanna get down there again.
You get better and better.
Who, I do?
Can I have a kiss?
I love this, you know
what I love about it?
- You wanna know?
- Yes.
I love the smooching, you know,
like necking quality of it.
That whole teenage thing,
I don't know what it...
It just does something to me.
I just love the idea and I'm doing it now
and I'm an old person.
An old drug-addicted junkie
and I got a girl and I
got my arm around her.
It's a terrific feeling.
It'll get better.
This won't get better than this,
I don't think it gets better than this.
I think so.
Wow.
What is that?
I wrote it.
Are you kidding?
You wrote that?
Have you ever tried to sell that?
No.
That's a best-seller.
Do you like me?
You'll do.
Do I look good in a mustache?
Why do you like me?
I don't know.
What do you want?
I wanna go back and get
my money from that creep.
I did the job, didn't I, right?
I risked 20 years, right?
I deserve to get paid.
He pays me, I'm gonna set him up.
It isn't the money, J.
We can always get money, what do you want?
What is it?
What do you want?
That corner.
Give me some money.
$25, is that enough?
J!
Come back home to me.
Sure.
Have you seen Billy?
Billy.
Hey, Billy.
Billy, it's J.
J, my baby, hello there, man.
I'm looking to score, what's happening?
It ain't nothin' happening down here, J.
I Know where we can score uptown.
Come on, let's go.
Come on, get your stuff.
Oh, J.
I thought you got popped, man.
I did get pop, but
I mouthed my way out.
If anybody can mouth, baby, you can!
I thought you was in the slammer.
Not so fast, not so fast, not so fast.
That looks like Little
Davey up there, man.
Yeah, that is Little Davey.
Hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it.
Pull over to the side there.
Davey, my man, how ya doin', bro?
Hey, what's happening, my man?
Hey, I wanna score, man.
Well, how much you wanna cop?
About half a load.
Well, all right, let
me check with my man.
Right, right.
What's happening?
Everything is cool.
Where'd he go?
To check his man out.
My man, Concepcion.
What's happening?
How much you cats got?
20.
$20 for half a load?
We can work it out.
Whoa, dig, man.
Alright, why don't you just cool it here,
and I'll check on my man, all right?
Right, right.
- I think I can get two more.
- Hey, listen,
it's all right, man.
He'll work it out.
He's got good stuff?
Hot shit, man.
Ask your man here.
Concepcion's a bitch.
It's all right.
This is a take-off.
Cool it now, we want everything youse got.
And just don't move and be cool.
Oh, shit, Davey, come on, man.
Oh, no, listen, man.
You know, I got a jones, man,
and you're the only people coming round.
I need the money, man.
Come on, put it in there.
Mean, it ain't that we
don't like y'all or nothing.
You know, we do a lot
of business together.
- Yeah, right.
- And we can still do some
but I mean I'm uptight today,
- you dig it, baby?
- Mm-hmm, yeah, I'm hip.
- I knew you'd understand.
- Hey, man,
will you leave us some car fare?
Hey, listen, man, can we
leave them some car fare?
They can walk.
Damn, Davey baby
who'd ever thought you
for a burn man, dammit?
- Coat.
- Man, it's cold outside.
Coat, coat.
Right, right, maybe you
want everything, right?
Yeah, everything.
Yeah, how about this?
Hold it, Davey!
Brother, dear, yeah.
Now what are you gonna say, huh?
That Concepcion guy's a bad mother, man.
- We've been doing business.
- Yeah, right.
- Come on, man.
- Where's my money?
You got to give me, hey, come on, man.
Oh, everything, every bit of.
- Hey, listen, man.
- Yeah.
Didn't I try to get you the car fare?
That's more than I'm gonna give you.
I'll tell you what to do,
you run up them steps,
you keep right on running,
you understand?
Hey, you turn back just
once, baby, and you're dead.
Put it there!
So you got nothing to
tell us about him, huh?
If I did, I would.
Talk and walk, that's my motto.
Well, then what's
your tie-in with him?
Hello and goodbye.
Hey, we want that mother bad, J.
So you're gonna take a fall.
You know, you're gonna sweat
and you're gonna scream.
Because we're gonna
plant you on a 2-20-20.
You'll plant me?
Yeah.
That's right, we want
Vivian on a sale, J.
What do you mean, you're gonna plant me?
What do you mean by that?
Do you know how much time you can get?
Do you know we can throw
away the key on you?
But we wanna keep you on the street
"cause that's the only way
we can get that rat-freako.
Yeah, we know where he lives,
who he does business with,
where they do business,
how they do business but
we gotta get him on a buy.
We wanna buy off the Geek, J.
I don't have that kind
of relationship with him.
Unless you tell us,
you're gonna take a pinch.
I'm clean.
I'm not holding, I'm clean.
You're holding out, bud.
Look, nobody's gonna know about,
all you gotta is ya tell
"em you got some friends
from outta town, they wanna
buy some heavy weight,
that's all, simple.
If I give him up, it's my life.
But with what we got on you,
you're gonna do 20 years minimum anyway.
You guys are scumbags.
J, why don't you give
me a call sometime?
I miss you.
Yeah, I will, I'll do that.
How much do you want?
I want a Ki.
That'll be about 20 thou.
It's gotta be at least.
It'll be pure.
There's stuff going around for about 16.
Yeah, there's stuff going around.
Okay, so your stuff is pure,
let's say we make a meet
at about 18, how's that?
You have the money with you?
You give me a taste,
I'll make a phone call.
If I sell you a ki of something
and you happen to be the wrong guy
then I'd do some heavy time.
Hey, come on, that's
why we got J here, right?
That's if I were selling
and JJ was setting me up.
You hear that, Jerome?
Jerome?
I think the only good
addict is a dead addict.
All right, what's the
story, we got a deal or what?
No, no.
Da-da!
Hey, baby.
Hey.
Hey, y'all.
Now, you see that?
Nothing.
Your Parm, man, she's really,
she's really together.
She sure is fine, man,
I mean, your chick Parm.
Nice chick, man, really nice
chick, and she digs you, man.
Yeah.
This cat who's bringing the
bag, you copped from him before?
Yeah, well, you know, like a while ago,
he used to hang with Long Willy.
And I sure hope it ain't no lemonade, man.
You know what I mean?
Hey.
You know, baby, I love this life.
Love it.
"Cause when we get up in the morning,
we know exactly what we gonna do next.
Hustle for another bag.
I wouldn't give it up for nothing.
No.
"Cause like we got a purpose in life,
you know what I mean?
How many people can really say that?
You wouldn't believe this, J,
but before I got into drugs, man,
I was like into myself, you know.
I couldn't go out and do things, man.
I had what you might call a complex.
Hey, man.
What's happening?
Same, what's happening?
Same thing, you know how that goes, man.
Yeah.
Be cool.
Later.
Hey, baby.
Hey.
Hey!
Hey, look here.
You speak English?
What's your name?
That's fantastic, baby!
She did it.
She gave me the date, you understand?
Hey, where do you think
I should take her, man?
Take her to 42nd Street,
take here to a movie.
Man, and have all them
dope fiends hitting on her?
No.
Hey, how about if I took her
to Radio City Music Hall?
Yeah, well, let me ask you this, man,
oh, what if I took her to
Jack Dempsey's for dinner?
- Have you ever been there?
- Yeah, yeah.
What's it like?
It's nice, nice, she'll like it.
You sure nobody's on this floor?
Positive.
Beautiful.
Wow, baby, this is out of sight.
It's tough, man.
Hey, where'd you find it?
Yeah, huh?
It's too much, baby.
Yeah, all right.
You know, it's a problem, man,
where to take a chick in this city.
I mean where do you take a girl
when you wanna make a
good impression on, huh?
To bed.
Go right to bed.
Jive. You always come up
with something like that.
I can never hold a serious
discussion wi' you, J.
You gotta learn to broaden yourself, baby.
Billy, Billy.
Yeah?
We got Spanish quarters.
No jive, huh?
One for two.
One for me, one for you.
Dig it!
Yeah.
I'm going first, right?
Who copped?
What do you mean you're going first?
Who copped last time?
Yeah, well, who went first last time?
You.
Yeah, yeah, I guess I did.
That's right.
I guess that leaves you.
Say what?
What's happening?
It's okay, it's okay.
Yeah, we good, there you go.
Yeah.
There you go, there you go.
Yes, indeed.
I need a gas too, man.
Why don't you bring the
old lady with us, man?
We go up together.
Okay.
You like that?
It might be a gas, man.
Take care of a little
business, you understand?
Do a little do.
Oobie-doo.
Oobie-doo-pooh!
You dig it?
Yeah.
All right.
Come on, man, hurry up.
It's coming.
Oh, yeah.
There it is, there it is.
Okay.
- Are you ready?
- Mm-hmm.
Here it comes.
Come on, come on.
- Billy, Billy.
- Yeah.
Thank you kindly, sir.
May God take a liking to you.
Yeah, mean, why don't you go with us,
dinner might be tough,
- you know.
- Yeah, maybe, maybe, maybe.
We go to Dempsey's
and have a good dinner,
then we go discothequing,
I'll tell you what I'm gonna do then.
Yeah.
I'm going to bed,
yeah, me and that chick!
Take me with you.
I mean, if you
don't wanna go to Demp.
Billy?
Billy.
Call my mother, man!
Call my mother, J!
Don't go out.
Billy, don't go out.
Billy, Billy, please,
please, don't go out.
Oh, my God.
We're leaving right now.
Billy's dead.
What happened?
He's dead.
They gave us a hot shot.
Hot shot?
What's that?
Battery acid, rat poison.
It was meant for me.
Pull over.
Why?
Just pull over,
I wanna do something.
Hey, J!
What is it?
What are you doing?
What the hell is this?
You're going down, J.
What for?
Don't ask me what for, you know.
Look, I'm clean, I'm
here with my girlfriend.
Wanna roll down the window?
Police.
What, is she a hooker?
No, she's a square kid.
Look, she's my fiancee.
Yeah, that looks like a hooker to me.
Is this your car??
Yes.
Where did you
get a car like this?
None of your business.
Hey, don't cop no
attitude with me, lady.
Has he got a warrant?
Have you got a warrant?
You're in big
trouble, sweetheart.
It's a plant.
Hey, that's a plant, you plant.
I'm gonna wreck you, you're planting her.
I'm gonna wreck you!
What?
I'm gonna wreck you with my mouth.
Harassment!
Police harassment!
What are you doing this for?
Weren't you suppose to
do something for us, J?
Yeah, I tried to make a deal,
but he wouldn't bite, ask Danny.
Danny.
We're gonna turn you loose,
but your girl is taking a bust now.
Oh, no, man, I'll take the bust.
Let me do it, please.
We want you out on the streets.
We want you on the streets.
Now, get outta here.
Now, get outta here!
J!
J.
You look tired.
Can I help you in any way?
I'm sorry, J,
for everything.
Say, man, you're in the light.
Why don't you move?
Geek, my man.
You've been a bad boy, Jerome.
Can you fix me up?
Sure, sure, I'd love to fix you.
I'll pay you soon as I can.
It's a gift.
What are my odds?
Your odds?
That it's not a hot shot.
So what if it is?
It'll be the best jolt you'll ever get.
You're the winner, aren't you?
Born to win.